<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Games, Management and the Fate of the Universe]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Games, Management and the Fate of the Universe]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/alvasvoboda/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 17:45:36 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/alvasvoboda/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>It's hard to figure out how much micromanagement (sometimes known as "paying attention") is too much. Keeping the game open too long itself draws Deathclaws and Mole Rats and Rad Roaches, and even random room fires.  But it's also possible to play helicopter manager, drop in once a day, and find that the staff are getting more and more demoralized because of lack of resources and general unhealthiness in the job environment -- and resources and unhealthiness are issues that require some direct engagement by a manager to resolve.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alvasvoboda/75507786-d8ab-4497-961e-713dafe14b90/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">75507786-d8ab-4497-961e-713dafe14b90</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 17:44:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Disasters that result in near-catastrophic loss of staff are not necessarily fatal; but conscious retrenchment is required.  In Fallout Shelter, Deathclaw attacks can results in loss of at least half of the population, whether you defend against the Deathclaws or just try to run and stay out of their way, if your Dwellers aren't well-fed and well-armed.  And it generally takes an evolutionary approach to building the resources that will get them to that well-fed and well-armed state, during which period a Deathclaw attack is likely to happen (at least if you've been a little silly about growing your team too quickly, taking on too much work at once).  So you've got to accept the inevitability of "disaster" and think about how you want to deal with it: I've tried at least three approaches, including letting the corpses lie around until I could revive them over a long period of time (this resulted in a bunch of my Dwellers and guns disappearing due to an apparent automatic cleanup that happens in the game after a few days); getting rid of the bodies immediately, and retrenching to a much smaller, leaner team that was capable of keeping itself alive until I could rebuild (this had disadvantages because of the number of empty rooms in the Vault, which tend to bring in Rad Roaches and Mole Rats that are just as dangerous to the overall population as Deathclaws, when not dealt with immediately); and getting rid of not only the bodies, but the rooms they inhabited as well, resigning myself to a long period of rebuilding but making sure I had the resources to support those who were left (the most successful approach by far, but one which requires a degree of detachment and taking the long view that I find it hard to achieve, either in a game or at work). </p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alvasvoboda/80cd7681-58ff-4839-8089-2f961bbe74f7/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">80cd7681-58ff-4839-8089-2f961bbe74f7</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 17:42:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>It's hard to keep track of the abilities of team members, and keep them working on the things that improve the "world" most.  Sometimes you just want people to work on what they're best at, sometimes you want them to acquire experience, and sometimes you're just looking for a place to keep them busy.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alvasvoboda/7e9b6912-6218-49af-a3bc-e5d6acfba737/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7e9b6912-6218-49af-a3bc-e5d6acfba737</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 17:44:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>I've been playing Fallout Shelter pretty obsessively for about a month now, on the principle that it will teach me something about my skills/responsibilities/dilemmas as a middle manager.  I have six Vaults that I manage (on my iPad and my iPhone, three each, that being the limit on a single device), which I equate to "teams" like the team I lead at the company I work for (a large Californian gas and electric utility).  Confirmation bias is definitely at work here, but I find the similarities between managing a Vault and managing a team salient.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/alvasvoboda/b151ef38-87a6-4104-a8fb-f29285e19b63/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b151ef38-87a6-4104-a8fb-f29285e19b63</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2016 17:43:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>